manageengine.com 2018-03-14

# ManageEngine Privacy Policy

5th February 2018

[www.webnms.com](http://www.webnms.com/), [www.manageengine.com](https://www.manageengine.com/) and [www.zoho.com](http://www.zoho.com/) are websites owned by ZOHO Corp..

**Our postal address is**

ZOHO Corp.  
4141 Hacienda Drive   
Pleasanton, CA 94588, USA

We can be reached via e-mail at [support@manageengine.com](mailto:support@manageengine.com), or you can reach ManageEngine Customer Support Services by telephone at +1-925-924-9500 and +1-888-720-9500 (Monday to Friday). 

##  General

At ManageEngine, a division of Zoho Corporation (hereinafter "ManageEngine"), we respect your need for online privacy and protection of personal information. This Privacy Policy Statement applies to [www.manageengine.com](https://www.manageengine.com/) website, ManageEngine suite of products, services, associated mobile applications and product or service specific websites. You can visit most areas of our websites without providing personal information. But at times we do need such information for providing access to products or services requested by you.

## ManageEngine On-Demand Solutions

We offer our cloud based IT management solutions under the brand name 'ManageEngine On-Demand Solutions'. Our privacy practices with respect to your use of our ManageEngine On-Demand Solutions will be in accordance with the privacy policy statement available at <https://ondemand.manageengine.com/privacy.html>. 

## Children's Online Privacy Protection

ManageEngine does not knowingly collect personal information from persons who are under 13 years of age. By agreeing to use our products or services, you represent that you are 13 years or older.

## Information we collect

When you express interest in our products or services or sign up for a ManageEngine service that requires registration, we ask you for your personal information such as your name and email address. You may also be asked to choose a unique username, a password, a security question and an answer to the security question. In addition, we collect information regarding the Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone and operating system of visitors to our websites. When you use our ManageEgine products or services, we collect usage related information which may occasionally include personal information such as your email address. In case of products or services requiring payment, we request credit card or other payment account information, which will be used solely for processing payments.

We use temporary and permanent cookies to enhance the experience on our websites. Temporary cookies will be removed from your computer each time you close your browser. By selecting keep me signed-in option, a permanent cookie will be stored in your computer and you will not have to sign-in by providing complete login information, each time you return to our website. If you have turned cookies off, you may not be able to use registered areas of the websites.

We partner with third parties to manage our advertisements on other websites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other websites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based advertisements, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). However, you will continue to receive generic advertisements on other websites that display advertisements.

We may receive information about you from other sources, including publicly available databases or third parties from whom we have purchased data, and combine this data with information we already have about you. This helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you. If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

## How we use Information

Your personal information such as name and email address is used to keep you informed on new products/versions/updates/service packs, upcoming events and changes in this Privacy Policy Statement. Any alternate email address, security question and the answer to the security question, if given, will be used solely for the purpose of resetting password.

Your Financial Information will not be stored by us except for the name and address of the card holder, the expiry date and the last four digits of the credit card number. Subject to your prior consent and where necessary for processing future payments, your financial information will be stored in encrypted form on secure servers of reputed. Payment Gateway Service Providers who are obliged to handle your personal information subject to appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We use Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone and operating system of visitors collected in our log files to analyze the trends, administer the websites and to track visitor's movements and to improve our applications.

The usage details we collect pertaining to your use of ManageEgine products or services will be used to improve our products or services.

When you purchase a ManageEngine product or service on behalf of your organization, we may publish your organizations name in the Customer List on our websites and in press releases, advertisements, brochures and other promotional materials. When you provide testimonials with respect to your use of ManageEngine products or services, we publish your name, designation in your organization, photo (if provided) on our websites and in press releases, advertisements, brochures and other promotional materials. You may contact us at [legal@manageengine.com](mailto:legal@manageengine.com) to request us not to use your testimonials.

We use cookies for easier access to our websites. Once you close your browser, the temporary cookies simply terminate, except for the permanent cookies created when you select the 'keep me signed-in' option.

## Links from our websites

Some pages of our websites contain external links. You are advised to verify the privacy practices of such other websites. We are not responsible for the manner of use or misuse of information made available by you at such other websites. We encourage you not to provide personal information, without assuring yourselves of the privacy practices of other websites.

## With whom we share Information

We have partners/affiliates/resellers for specific products and services. We may share generic aggregated demographic information with our business partners / affiliates / resellers and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. Your name and email address may occasionally be shared with our business partners/ affiliates/resellers in connection with our products/services and any use of your personal information by such business partners/affiliates/resellers will be in accordance with this Privacy Policy Statement.

## How secure is your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password and transaction information. Access to your name and email address is restricted to our employees, contractors, business partners, affiliates and resellers who need to know such information in connection with our products and services and are bound by confidentiality obligations.

## Your Choice in Information Use

We will obtain your prior consent for use of your personal information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected or the purposes described in this Privacy Policy Statement. In such cases we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of your personal information for those other purposes. From time to time, we may send emails to you regarding new products, services, releases and upcoming events. You may opt out of receiving newsletters and other secondary messages from ManageEngine by selecting the 'unsubscribe' function present in every email we send. However, when you have purchased products or services from us, you are not allowed to opt out from receiving information on versions/updates/service packs.

## Accessing, Updating and Removing Personal Information

Upon request we provide customers with access to their personal information free of charge. Customers may correct, update or remove any such personal information either through the customers' profile, if they have an account with ManageEngine or by contacting ManageEngine Customer Support Services. Such changes may take up to 48 hours to take effect.

## Mobile Application

When you download and use our mobile applications, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, device status and the device identifier to provide and improve our mobile applications.

We send you push notifications from time-to-time when you elect to receive notifications. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we will need to collect certain information about your device such as operating system and customer identification information. If you no longer wish to receive notifications, you may turn them off at the device level.

Subject to explicit consent, some of our mobile applications have access to camera, call history, contact information, geographic location, photo library, etc. Our applications require such access to provide services related to the relevant mobile application.

Some of our mobile applications collect location based information subject to explicit consent. We will only share this information with our mapping provider for the sole purpose of mapping customer location. You may opt-out of location based services at any time by editing the setting at the device level or by emailing us at [legal@manageengine.com](mailto:legal@manageengine.com).

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile applications installed on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We link the information we store within the analytics software to personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile application for debugging purposes.

## Enforcement of Privacy Policy 

We make every effort including periodic reviews to ensure that personal information provided by you is used in conformity with this Privacy Policy Statement. If you have any concerns regarding our adherence to this policy or the manner in which personal information is used on our website, kindly contact ManageEngine Customer Support Services at [support@manageengine.com](mailto:support@manageengine.com). We will contact you to address your concerns and we will also co-operate with regulatory authorities in this regard.

## Notification of Changes 

Any changes to our Privacy Policy Statement will be posted on our website in order to keep you informed of any changes in nature of information collected and manner of collection, use and sharing of information. If at any point we decide to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at <https://www.manageengine.com/privacy.html> periodically.

## End of Privacy Policy

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy Statement, please contact us at [legal@manageengine.com](mailto:legal@manageengine.com).

Thank you for reaching out! We'll get in touch with you shortly.
